Use the file “childrenoftheelements.keystore” as keystone to publish this app on Play Store. 

If another keystore file is used, you must publish the app as a new one from scratch, loosing all reviews and users.


The permissions for this keystone are:


alias

CoE_Alias

password :

COE_6bin8am6jem5dyt6el

first and last name:

carlos solis

organization
children of elements

organization unit
children of elements

city
Santiago

state
Santiago

country
CL
